<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Deive Leal</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Deive Leal</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 16:00:00 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Common Table Expression or Just CTE</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blogs/common-table-expression-or-just-cte/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 16:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blogs/common-table-expression-or-just-cte/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When I started my studies in sql to handle data from databases many things seemed confused and messed up. The use of nested queries or subqueries was kind of confusing. The longer the query is more difficult, it is to understand what it does. Consequently, its reading, debugging and maintenance are equally difficult. For instance, imagine a code with seven or more different subqueries. The limit is your imagination. But, the more subqueries you have, more business rules can be applied and, consequently, the challenge to maintain them increases. To help us with this great problem, a good option is to use common table expressions or aka cte.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Entrepreneurship</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blogs/about-entrepreneurship/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 20:23:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blogs/about-entrepreneurship/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Entrepreneurship is such a magic word that can either change reality or, it is at least, what some people think it does. With hype words and sex meaning, many people believe that entrepreneurship it’s the key to develop or increase value in society.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It seems that people create a mythology around the entrepreneur and their performance on a regular basis. Anyone can be an entrepreneur, investing time and money and success is guaranteed.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image Gallery</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/gallery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 18:35:46 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/gallery/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Emoji Support</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/emoji-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 22:53:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/emoji-support/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Emoji can be enabled in a Hugo project in a number of ways. :zap:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;emoji-support&#34;&gt;Emoji Support&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/functions/emojify/&#34;&gt;emojify&lt;/a&gt; function can be called directly in templates or &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/templates/shortcode-templates/#inline-shortcodes&#34;&gt;Inline Shortcodes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To enable emoji globally, set &lt;code&gt;enableEmoji&lt;/code&gt; to &lt;code&gt;true&lt;/code&gt; in your site’s &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/getting-started/configuration/&#34;&gt;configuration&lt;/a&gt; and then you can type emoji shorthand codes directly in content files; e.g.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.emoji-cheat-sheet.com/&#34;&gt;Emoji cheat sheet&lt;/a&gt; is a useful reference for emoji shorthand codes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;N.B.&lt;/strong&gt; The above steps enable Unicode Standard emoji characters and sequences in Hugo, however the rendering of these glyphs depends on the browser and the platform. To style the emoji you can either use a third party emoji font or a font stack; e.g.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
